triadmedianetwork.com 2019-05-09

# Triad Media

**Privacy**

**Information Collection And Use**

Triad Media is the sole owner of the information collected. Triad Media Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Affiliates**

We use LinkTrust affiliate management software. We do not collect any information other than what is collected via the LinkTrust system. You can access the site at www.linktrust.com.

Information Use Profile

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to keep track of a user's order when they move through our site. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies are required for ordering from Triad Media. See http://www.cookiecentral.com/faq/ for more information.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are tied to users' personally identifiable information to allow us to keep track of the orders of users that have entered our site via third-party advertising. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new customers a welcoming email to verify their password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Send an email to [legal@triadmedia.com](mailto:legal@triadmedia.com)[](mailto:info@triadmedianetwork.com)

**Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users' wishes.

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable) We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, we do store aggregate data so that we provide outside sources with general traffic statistics from our website (for example, we may use aggregate information in a press release that states "traffic at Triad Media increased 40% this week.")

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information, the user is on a secure page hosted by Directtrack.com, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://wp.netscape.com/security/techbriefs/ssl.html. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [legal@triadmedia.com](mailto:legal@triadmedia.com)[](mailto:info@triadmedianetwork.com).

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at [legal@triadmedia.com](mailto:legal@triadmedia.com)[](mailto:info@triadmedianetwork.com).

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.

**Contact Information**

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Triad Media Inc.   
848 N. Rainbow Blvd. Suite 1680  
Las Vegas, NV 89107
